A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Tobacco and Flour Inspector Records, 1776-1878
Library of Virginia
- Series IX: Public Tobacco Warehouse vouchers, 1776-1865 (APA 293)., Extent: XX cubic feet. (Box XX-XX)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's Warehouse), 1835 Dec 9. (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Moore's Warehouse), 1836 Jan 14. (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1836 Feb 3. (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1836 Apr 7. (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1836 June 16. (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1836 June 17. (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1836 Aug 11. (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1836 Oct 19. (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1836 Oct 21. (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1836 Nov 8. (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1836 Nov 18. (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Vouchers (Liberty Warehouse), 1836 Dec 24. (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1837 Feb 9. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1837 Mar 2. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1837 Apr 6. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1837 May 9. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1837 Aug 15. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1837 Oct 4. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1837 Oct 17. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1837 Oct 21. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1837 Nov 1. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Unknown Warehouse), 1837 Nov 4. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1837 Dec 7. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1838 Jan 9. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1838 Feb 21. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1838 Sept 15. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1838 Oct 17. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1838 Oct 20. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1838 Nov 20. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1838 Nov 28. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1839 Jan 11. (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Tye River Warehouse), 1839 Jan 24. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1839 Mar 6. (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Botetourt and Buchanan County Warehouses), 1839 Mar 20. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1839 July 5. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1839 Aug 17. (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1839 Oct 11. (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1839 Oct 31. (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1839 Dec 11. (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1840 Apr 9. (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1840 Aug 6. (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Union Warehouse), 1840 Oct 9. (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Petersuburg Warehouses), 1840 Oct 23. (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1840 Nov 16. (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1840 Dec 30. (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1841 Mar 5. (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1841 July 8. (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1841 July 9. (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Uhknown Warehouse), 1841 Oct 22. (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Lynhburg Warehouses), 1841 Oct 29. (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1841 Jan 25. (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1842 Jan 25. (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1842 Apr 8. (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1842 Oct 8. (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1842 Oct 11. (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1842 Nov 7. (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1842 Dec 31. (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Liberty Warehouse), 1843 Jan 3. (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Friends Warehouse), 1843 Jan 25. (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1843 July 13. (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1843 Oct 6. (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Lyncburg Warehouses), 1843 Oct 25. (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Venable Warehouse), 1843 Oct 25. (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1843 Nov 23. (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1844 Apr 5. (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1844 Oct 28. (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Friends and Liberty Warehouses), 1844 Nov 15. (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Martin's Warehouse), 1844 Nov 19. (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1845 Feb 25. (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Royster's Warehouse), 1845 Mar 11. (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1845 Apr 11. (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Tye River Warehouse), 1845 Apr 24. (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1845 Oct 13. (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1845 Oct 24. (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1845 Nov 8. (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1846 Apr 11. (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1846 Oct 26. (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1846 Oct 27. (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1847 Apr 9. (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1847 Oct 23. (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1847 Oct 30. (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1848 Jan 24. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1848 Apr 7. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 May 11. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 May 18. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 May 20. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 June 13. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 June 16. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 June 17. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 July 10. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 July 17. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1848 Oct 6. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 Oct 14. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1848 Oct 23. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 Dec 2. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1848 Dec 5. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1849 Apr 2. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1849 Oct 18. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1849 Dec 17. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1850 Jan 23. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1850 Apr 6. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1850 Dec 30. (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1851 Jan 4. (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1851 Oct 27. (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Dinwiddie County Warehouses), 1852 Jan 3. (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1852 Mar 24. (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1852 Dec 20. (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1853 Jan 3. (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Tye River Warehouse), 1853 Jan 21. (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1853 Jan 22. (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1853 June 4. (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1853 Aug 9. (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1853 Nov 1. (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1853 Oct 10. (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1853 Oct 12. (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1854 Jan 23. (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1854 Mar 14. (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1854 Mar 18. (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Unknown Warehouse), 1854 June 3. (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1854 June 30. (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1855 Nov 8. (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1856 Jan 18. (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1856 Feb 1. (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1856 Mar 10. (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook and Shockoe Warehouses), 1856 Mar 14. (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1856 Nov 8. (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1856 Dec 12. (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1857 Jan 14. (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1857 Dec 12. (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1858 Jan 16. (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Unknown Warehouse), 1858 July 7. (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1858 Sept 9. (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1859 Sept 14. (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1859 Dec 17. (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1859 Dec 23. (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1860 Jan 10. (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1860 June 11. (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Henrico County and Richmond Warehouses), 1860 Oct 6. (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1860 Oct 6. (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1861 June 11. (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1861 Sept 6. (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1862 Apr 16. (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1862 July 16. (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1862 Sept 20. (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1863 Jan 15. (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1863 July 22. (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1863 Sept 17. (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1864 Jan 14. (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1865 Jan 13. (Box 17, Folder 68)